[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Guys! Peyton Pittman just posted his jet is about to
大家！Peyton Pittman刚刚发帖说他的喷气式飞机即将
fly over the store!
飞过商店上空！
[gasps]
[倒吸气]
No way!
不可能！
Who's Peyton Pittman?
Peyton Pittman是谁？
Uh, young hotshot tech billionaire.
呃，年轻的科技亿万富翁。
International ladies' man.
国际女性杀手。
[Ricky and Dicky] Basically me with money.
[Ricky和Dicky]基本上就是有钱的我。
You wish. No, you wish!
你想得美。不，你想得美！
Stop saying what I'm saying!
别再说我说的话了！
Jambalaya! Pants! Tractor-face!
什锦饭！裤子！拖拉机脸！
[all] Whoa.
[所有人] 哇。
Guys, hurry up!
伙计们，快点！
- I heard the inside of his jet is wallpapered with money.
- 我听说他的飞机内部是用钱贴的墙纸。
- I heard the outside is covered in gold.
- 我听说外部是镀金的。
- It can't be covered in gold.
- 不可能是镀金的。
[jet flying overhead]
[飞机从头顶飞过]
[all] Ooh--ahh!
[所有人] 哦——啊！
[all] Ooh.
[所有人] 哦。
The legends are true.
传说果然是真的。
I wish I was stupid rich like that.
我真希望自己能那么有钱。
If I was stupid rich, I'd buy an island.
如果我那么有钱，我会买一座岛。
- I'd buy two islands. - Why do you need two islands?
- 我会买两座岛。 - 你为什么需要两座岛？
I'm gonna need a vacation island.
我需要一座度假岛。
A dude's gotta relax.
男人得放松一下。
- Oh, hey, have you kids seen your father?
- 哦，嘿，你们这些孩子见过你们的爸爸吗？
He asked me to bring out all these shoes.
他让我把这些鞋子都拿出来。
- Hello, family! [all shout]
- 大家好！ [大家喊]
Look at this busy mom,
看看这位忙碌的妈妈，
so exhausted from lugging around all of the footwear
拖着所有这些鞋走来走去，她累坏了
for her children's various athletic activities.
为了孩子们的各种体育活动。
There's got to be a better way.
一定有更好的办法。
- She could use a bag. - Or a basket. - Or a box. - Or a supportive husband.
- 她可以用一个包。 - 或者一个篮子。 - 或者一个盒子。 - 或者一个支持她的丈夫。
Well, now there is.
现在有了。
Introducing my latest invention, Choez.
介绍一下我的最新发明，Choez。
Did you just say you invented shoes?
你刚才说你发明了鞋子？
Yes, that's right, Choez,
是的，没错，Choez，
the shoes that can be anything you choose!
这些鞋子可以是你选择的任何东西！
The name needs work.
名字需要改进。
You should call 'em Sweet Foot Rides.
你应该叫它们‘甜足之旅’。
- Ice skating, you say? Why not?
冰上滑行，你是说？为什么不呢？
Just choose the ice skating attachment.
只需选择冰上滑行的配件。
Or choose from these many other attachment options.
或者从这些其他多种配件选项中选择。
Wow, Tom, this might be your best idea yet.
哇，汤姆，这可能是你目前为止最好的主意。
You'd like me to demonstrate them? Why, sure!
你想让我演示一下吗？当然可以！
Now watch...
现在看着...
as I... choose...
我...选择...
to leap into the future... of Choez!
跃入Choez的未来...
Somebody throw me an alley-oop!
有人给我来个空中接力！
[loud crash]
[巨大的撞击声]
He got nothing but net.
他一球未失，全中。
Well, at least the shoes worked.
嗯，至少鞋子起作用了。
They definitely did.
确实如此。
He got sick air!
他跳得真高！
Where did that come from?
这从哪儿来的？
Guys, dad's shoes could be our ticket to stupid rich town.
伙计们，老爸的鞋子可能是我们通往超级富豪镇的门票。
Stupid Rich Town!
超级富豪镇！
That's what I'm gonna call my second island.
那将是我第二个岛屿的名字。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ [口哨旋律] ♪
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping]
♪ [有节奏的拍手] ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪ - ♪ One, two ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪ ♪ 一，二 ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
Dad, your Choez are amazing.
爸爸，你的Choez太神奇了。
They gave you mad hops.
它们让你跳得老高了。
I don't even know what those words mean!
我甚至不知道这些词是什么意思！
So when are you gonna start selling them?
那你什么时候开始卖它们呢？
Oh, Choez are nowhere near ready to sell.
哦，Choez还没准备好出售呢。
This is my only pair, and they still need a bit of work.
这是我唯一的一双，它们还需要一些改进。
What are you talking about? You're straight trippin', yo!
你在说什么呢？你简直是疯了，兄弟！
Who am I?
我是谁？
Yeah, just go make some more, slap 'em in a box,
对，再去多做几双，装进盒子里，
bada-bing, bada-boom, we buy some islands.
叮咚，叮咚，我们买几座岛。
It's not that easy, Dicky.
没那么简单，迪基。
It takes years to perfect a product like this.
像这样的产品，完善它需要好几年。
Come on, Dad, you're always coming up
拜托，爸，你总是发明这些伟大的东西，却从不去尝试卖掉它们。
with these great inventions, and you never try to sell them.
哦，记得那些末端带勺子的筷子吗？
Oh, remember the chopsticks with the spoons on the end?
是啊，结果那些只是长勺子。
Yeah, turns out those were just long spoons.
那末端带勺子的鼓槌呢？
What about the drumsticks with spoons on the end?
也是长勺子。
Also long spoons.
专注于你擅长的！鞋子！
Focus on what you're good at! Shoes!
啊，听着，我没时间跟你们扯这些，孩子们。
Ah, look, I don't have time for this, kids.
啊，听着，孩子们，我没时间处理这些。
Doyle Thomas from Apollo is coming here today
今天阿波罗的道尔·托马斯要来这里
to check out the new displays.
检查新的展示。
W-w-wait, a guy from Apollo Footwear is coming here?
等等，阿波罗鞋业的一个人要来这里？
This is your chance, Dad.
这是你的机会，爸爸。
Show 'em those shoes, and we'll all be rich!
展示那些鞋子，我们都会变富的！
Kids, I appreciate your support,
孩子们，我感谢你们的支持，
but you can't get rich overnight.
但你们不能一夜之间变富。
Besides, I'm just not ready to show him the shoes.
而且，我只是还没准备好向他展示那些鞋子。
Come on, you seemed so ready a minute ago.
拜托，你刚才看起来还那么有准备。
Yeah, to show you guys, but not him, not today.
是的，给你们看，但不是他，不是今天。
Hey, guys. [sneezes]
嘿，伙计们。[打喷嚏]
- Bless you. - Thank you, Ricky.
- 保佑你。 - 谢谢你，Ricky。
- Hmm? - What?
- 嗯？ - 什么？
- I sneezed. - That's okay.
- 我打喷嚏了。 - 没关系。
I know that's okay, it's just, you didn't say "bless you."
我知道没关系，只是，你没说'保佑你'。
That's 'cause Ricky got it.
那是因为Ricky已经说了。
He's the fastest bless in the west.
他是西方最快的保佑者。
No, I know, but you know, it'd be nice if
不，我知道，但你知道，如果偶尔我丈夫能说'保佑你'，那就太好了。
once in a while my husband said "bless you."
哦，好吧，对不起。保佑你。
Oh, okay, I'm sorry. Bless you.
I didn't sneeze.
我没有打喷嚏。
Well, the next time you do,
嗯，下次你打喷嚏时，
you'll already have one in the bless you bank.
你已经在保佑银行里存了一个。
- Not a thing, Tom. - Sure, it is.
没什么，汤姆。
I just opened an account, and you know what?
当然有。
It comes with free hugging.
我刚开了一个账户，你知道吗？
Hmm? [chuckles]
它还附带免费拥抱。
Save a hug for me, Tommy!
嗯？[轻笑]
Doylee!
给我留个拥抱，汤米！
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
Oh, how's business?
哦，生意怎么样？
Oh, well, you know, there's no business like shoe business.
哦，你知道的，没有生意比得上鞋业。
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
Look at him over there, not making us rich!
看他在那边，没让我们发财！
Get this: I'm staying at the Chateau Chantelle.
告诉你，我住在尚特尔城堡。
I'm in Le Doorbell Suite.
我在门铃套房。
Oh, man, I wish I knew what it sounded like
哦，天哪，我真想知道拥有门铃套房的钱是什么声音。
to have Doorbell Suite money.
他本可以的，只要他听我们的。
He could if he just listened to us.
我们得帮他。
We gotta help him.
♪ Dingdong dingdong ♪
♪叮咚叮咚♪
[Tom and Doyle] ♪ Dongding dingdong ♪
[汤姆和多伊尔] ♪咚叮叮咚♪
- Hey, Dad, I've-- - We're in the middle of kind of an important meeting here, kids.
- 嘿，爸爸，我—— - 孩子们，我们正在开一个重要的会议。
- Is that really what it sounds like? - I'm not kidding, you got to come by and check it out!
- 那真的是它的声音吗？ - 我不是在开玩笑，你得过来亲自看看！
I would love that!
我非常愿意！
That's it. If Dad won't try to sell his shoes, we will.
就这样。如果爸爸不愿意卖他的鞋子，我们就来。
Yeah. We have to convince Doyle that every kid
是的。我们必须说服多伊尔，镇上每个孩子
in town is gonna want a pair of Dad's...
都会想要爸爸的一双……
uh, what'd he call them again?
呃，他怎么称呼它们来着？
- Uh, Choez! - Bless you.
- 呃，Choez！ - 保佑你。
♪ ♪
The Apollo display's looking great, Tommy Boy!
Apollo展示看起来很棒，Tommy Boy！
Dad!
爸爸！
There's a raccoon in your office.
你办公室里有只浣熊。
And he's on your computer.
而且他在用你的电脑。
He can type?
他会打字？
Not well.
不太好。
Excuse me, I have to deal with this.
对不起，我得处理这个。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Here I come!
我来了！
Uh, Mr. Thomas? Before you go, we need to show you something.
呃，托马斯先生？在你走之前，我们需要给你看一样东西。
- Something new. - Something incredible.
新的东西。
Something that's gonna bring in the Benjamins, boy-ee!
令人难以置信的东西。
Sorry.
能带来大把钞票的东西，伙计！
In this box is a shoe that will change
抱歉。
the athletic footwear game forever.
这个盒子里有一双鞋，它将永远改变运动鞋的游戏规则。
One shoe with changeable bottoms
一双带有可更换底部的鞋，适用于所有运动。
that does it all for every sport.
我们的爸爸发明的。
Our dad invented them.
他决定称它们为...
And he chooses to call them...
而他决定称它们为...
Sweet Foot Rides.
甜足之旅。
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow down there, Quad Squad.
哇，哇，哇。慢点，四人组。
I mean, Sweet Foot Rides is a pretty cool name,
我是说，甜足之旅是个很酷的名字，
but I'm sure your daddy-o would have told me about 'em
但我确信你老爸会告诉我的
if he wanted me to know, so I don't think this is for me.
如果他想让我知道，所以我觉得这不适合我。
Uh, would you excuse us for sec? Quaddle up!
呃，能让我们单独待一会儿吗？快集合！
We're losing him, guys. What do we do?
我们要失去他了，伙计们。我们该怎么办？
Promise him an island!
答应给他一个岛！
Maybe we should go get Dad and tell him
也许我们应该去找爸爸，告诉他
Doyle already loves the name.
多伊尔已经很喜欢这个名字了。
No, he'll be mad we went behind his back.
不，他会因为我们背着他做事而生气。
And when he finds out that I put a real raccoon in the office.
而且当他发现我把一只真正的浣熊放在办公室里。
[Dawn, Ricky, and Nicky] You what?
[黎明，瑞奇和尼基] 你做了什么？
You want a gold plane or not?
你到底要不要那架金色飞机？
Uh, guys? Doyle's gone.
呃，伙计们？多伊尔不见了。
And so are the Sweet Foot Rides!
还有那些甜足骑行也不见了！
He stole them!
他偷走了它们！
Homeboy just schooled us like a bunch of chumps.
这家伙把我们像一群笨蛋一样教训了一顿。
I need to lie down.
我需要躺下来休息一下。
♪ ♪
Hey, kids.
嘿，孩子们。
Hey, Mom, you know, we have a question for you.
嘿，妈妈，你知道，我们有个问题想问你。
- Let's say... - Hypothetically.
- 比如说... - 假设性地。
That we had a sweet boxed lunch, say a ham sandwich.
假设我们有一个美味的盒饭，比如说火腿三明治。
- I don't like ham. - Okay, fine, it's turkey.
- 我不喜欢火腿。 - 好吧，行，是火鸡。
I don't care for turkey.
我不喜欢火鸡。
Fine, it's leftover pizza.
好吧，是剩下的披萨。
I'm more of a soup man.
我更喜欢汤。
The point is... somebody took it.
关键是... 有人拿走了它。
Wait, wait, somebody stole your lunch?
等等，等等，有人偷了你的午餐？
- Hypothetically. - Who was it?
- 假设性的。 - 是谁？
Was it that Lewis?
是那个刘易斯吗？
Let's not point hypothetical fingers.
我们不要随便指责。
But the bottom line is... is it wrong to take back
但关键在于...拿回被偷的东西有错吗？
something that was stolen from you?
嗯，假设性的情况下，没错。
Well, hypothetically, no.
但如果真的是刘易斯偷了你的午餐，
But, if that Lewis really did steal your lunch,
那么，对不起，我恐怕得给他妈妈打电话——
then, I'm sorry, I'm going to have to call his mo--
我连糖霜都没来得及涂！
I didn't even get to frost them!
谢谢，妈妈。
Thanks, Mom.
[phone line ringing]
[电话铃声]
[Lewis on phone] Hello?
[Lewis在电话中] 喂？
Oh, hello, Lewis.
哦，你好，Lewis。
Is your mother there?
你妈妈在吗？
♪ ♪
Here it is, the Doorbell Suite.
这就是，门铃套房。
How are we gonna get in?
我们怎么进去？
I got this.
我有办法。
[gasps] You don't just ring the bell!
[惊呼] 你不能直接按门铃！
Yeah, what if he answers?
是啊，万一他来开门怎么办？
That's when we kick him in the shins and steal
那我们就踢他小腿，抢回
the Sweet Foot Rides back.
那些甜脚骑行工具。
That's not the plan.
那不是计划。
Oh. Okay, then I'll follow your lead.
哦。好吧，那我跟着你走。
- Hide! [doorbell chimes]
躲起来！[门铃响]
What kind of plan is this?
这是什么计划？
Okay, now that we know that he's not in there,
好了，既然知道他不在里面，
all we have to do is get inside.
我们只需要想办法进去。
Maybe we can get the housekeeper to let us in.
也许我们可以让女佣放我们进去。
- Yeah. - Good idea!
- 是的。 - 好主意！
We'll just tell her we're locked out and start crying.
我们就告诉她我们被锁在外面了，然后开始哭。
Everybody knows housekeepers can't stand crying.
大家都知道，女佣最受不了别人哭了。
Where'd you hear that?
你从哪儿听说的？
Oh, the magazines in Mom's bathroom basket.
哦，妈妈浴室篮子里的杂志上。
I've learned lots of things.
我学到了很多东西。
We don't need to cry.
我们不需要哭。
All we have to do is tell her we're locked out.
我们只需要告诉她我们被锁在外面了。
Um, excuse me, miss? We had a--
呃，打扰一下，小姐？我们有个——
[all] Oh.
[所有人] 哦。
Why does everybody assume I'm a woman?
为什么每个人都认为我是女性？
Men can be housekeepers too.
男性也可以是管家。
You're right, we've insulted both men and women housekeepers
你说得对，我们无意中的概括既侮辱了男性管家也侮辱了女性管家。
with our thoughtless generalization.
我们的道歉... Leslie。
Our apologies... Leslie.
男性也可以叫Leslie。
Men can be named Leslie too.
好吧，不管怎样，我们是Thomas家的孩子，我们的爸爸忘了给我们钥匙，你介意让我们进去吗？
Okay, anyway, we're the Thomas kids, and our dad forgot
抱歉，这违反了酒店政策。
to give us the keys, so would you mind letting us in?
[假装哭泣]
Sorry, it's against hotel policy.
好吧，好吧，我会让你们进去的。
[fake sobbing]
别哭了，我受不了哭泣。
Okay, okay, I'll let you in.
好吧，好吧，我让你们进来。
Just stop. I can't stand crying.
别哭了。我受不了别人哭。
Told ya.
我早说过了。
Whoa... and I thought the doorbell was nice!
哇...我还以为门铃已经够好了！
There's the box right on top of that huge bed.
那个大床上面就是箱子。
We all know what we need to do.
我们都知道我们需要做什么。
- Okay. Now let's get the box. - Yeah.
- 好的。现在让我们拿箱子。 - 对。
[door unlocks] - Someone's at the door!
- 有人敲门！
- I'll get it. - No, hide!
- 我去开。 - 不，快躲起来！
Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
♪ Dingdong dingdong ♪
♪叮咚叮咚♪
We gotta get the Sweet Foot Rides.
我们得拿到甜脚骑行券。
All right, that's it. It's shin kicking time.
好了，就这样。现在是踢腿时间。
Does anyone smell sweet and sour pork?
有人闻到糖醋排骨的味道吗？
There's no kicking. We're not hooligans.
没有踢腿。我们不是流氓。
[sniffs] Definitely sweet and sour pork.
（嗅）绝对是糖醋排骨。
[cell phone rings]
（手机铃声响起）
Hey, boss.
嘿，老板。
No, I am done with my sales meetings.
不，我已经结束了我的销售会议。
I'm not going anywhere for the rest of the night.
今晚剩下的时间我哪儿也不去。
Was there anything in Mom's magazine
妈妈杂志里有什么能帮我们摆脱困境的吗？
that could get us out of this?
没有，但我确实知道十种有益心脏健康的拉伸动作
No, but I do know ten heart-healthy stretches
是我们每天都应该做的。
that we should all be doing every day.
哎。
[sighs]
♪ ♪
然后...放松。
And...release.
啊。
[all] Ahh.
我真的很需要这个。
I really needed that.
好吧，现在我们该怎么办？
All right, now what do we do?
锻炼臀肌！
Work the glutes!
No! About getting out of here.
不！关于如何离开这里。
[Doyle] I got big news, boss.
[多伊尔] 老板，我有重大消息。
Shh! He's got big news!
嘘！他有重大消息！
I just got my hands on a prototype
我刚刚拿到了一个原型
of a hot, new, multiuse sport shoe
一款热门的、全新的多功能运动鞋
that could change the footwear game forever.
可能会永远改变鞋类游戏。
Do you think he's talking about Sweet Foot Rides?
你觉得他是在说甜蜜脚步骑行鞋吗？
I'm talking about Sweet Foot Rides.
我说的就是甜蜜脚步骑行鞋。
Yeah, come by the hotel before you fly out tonight.
对，今晚你飞之前来酒店一趟。
You can grab the shoes and take them back to the office.
你可以拿上鞋子，带回办公室。
[all gasp]
[所有人都惊讶地吸气]
Very well.
很好。
[water running]
[水流声]
That's the shower. Now's our chance.
那是淋浴间。现在是我们行动的机会。
Let's grab the box and get out of here!
我们快拿上盒子离开这里！
♪ ♪
Okay, now let's get out of here.
好了，现在我们离开这里。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, wait! Let's leave something lame in the box
哦，等等！我们在盒子里留点无聊的东西
to embarrass Doyle in front of his boss.
为了在Doyle的老板面前让他难堪。
Yeah!
好主意！
Ooh, how about the hotel slippers?
哦，酒店的拖鞋怎么样？
Oh, yeah!
哦，对！
Oh, come on!
哦，拜托！
All right. Now let's go.
好吧。现在我们走吧。
Ow, my glute!
哎哟，我的臀肌！
This is why we stretch, people!
这就是为什么我们要做拉伸，大家！
♪ ♪
So naturally, that Lewis's mom is totally taking his side
所以自然地，Lewis的妈妈完全站在他那边
on the whole lunch thing.
在整个午餐事件上。
Oh, get this, supposedly, they're in Florida.
哦，听说了吗，据说他们在佛罗里达。
Pfft.
噗。
They are in Florida.
他们的确在佛罗里达。
You've been watering their plants and taking in their mail.
你一直在给他们浇花和收邮件。
Haven't you?
不是吗？
I will be right back.
我马上回来。
[sneezes] Tom?
打喷嚏声] 汤姆？
What? Remember, you have one in the bless you bank.
什么？记得，你在‘保佑你’银行里有一个。
Ohh!
哦！
- [sneezes] - Bless you.
- [打喷嚏] - 保佑你。
Oh! Thank you... Ricky.
哦！谢谢你... 瑞奇。
Okay, how am I supposed to compete with that?
好吧，我该怎么跟他竞争呢？
When I was his age, I was blessing 'em two at a time!
我像他这么大的时候，一次保佑两个！
Hey, kids! Come over here. Welcome home.
嘿，孩子们！过来这里。欢迎回家。
Um, nothing.
呃，没什么。
We just went to the laundromat, and, um...
我们刚去了自助洗衣店，然后，呃...
Uh, won a laundry contest they were having!
呃，赢了一个他们正在举办的洗衣比赛！
We folded under pressure.
我们在压力下折叠。
[all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
Well, congratulations on your win.
嗯，恭喜你们获胜。
Now, I've got a story you are not gonna believe.
现在，我有一个你们不会相信的故事。
This morning, after I couldn't find the raccoon in the office,
今天早上，我在办公室找不到那只浣熊之后，
I saw the Sweet Foot Rides box
我看到了柜台上的Sweet Foot Rides盒子，
on the counter and thought, "My kids are right.
心想，“我的孩子们是对的。
Tommy's tired of not getting his."
Tommy厌倦了得不到他的。”
So I kissed my huge muscles, marched up to that box,
所以我亲吻了我那巨大的肌肉，大步走向那个盒子，
and grabbed it off the counter to go present my shoes to Doyle.
从柜台上抓起它，准备去向Doyle展示我的鞋子。
[applause]
[掌声]
I was so proud of my courageous decision,
我为自己的勇敢决定感到非常自豪，
I heroically skipped out of the store to find him.
我英勇地跳出商店去找他。
- You really skipped? - On the inside.
- 你真的跳着出去的？ - 在内心深处。
- People clapped? - On the inside.
- 人们鼓掌了？ - 在内心深处。
You kissed your muscles?
你亲吻了你的肌肉？
Look, I did not question your laundromat story.
听着，我没有质疑你的洗衣店故事。
The point is, Doyle loved my idea so much,
关键是，Doyle非常喜欢我的主意，
he's presenting the prototype to his boss tonight.
他今晚就要把原型展示给他的老板。
And, Dicky, he loved the name Sweet Foot Rides.
而且，Dicky，他很喜欢‘甜足之旅’这个名字。
I do have a knack for naming things.
我确实擅长给事物命名。
How about a nickname for the old man?
给老头起个绰号怎么样？
I'm thinking... The Skipper.
我在想... 船长。
Nailed it.
说中了。
Look at The Skipper go.
看船长行动。
Dicky, don't you see what this means?
迪基，你没看到这意味着什么吗？
All right, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Bowl Cut, Toilet Hog, Tiny Pants.
碗头，厕所霸，小裤裤。
No, not nicknames.
不，不是绰号。
We gotta get the real Sweet Foot Rides back in the box.
我们得把真正的甜足之旅放回盒子里。
You're right, Bowl Cut.
你说得对，碗头。
Let's go save The Skipper.
我们去救船长吧。
♪ ♪
[all fake crying] - Thank you, Leslie!
（所有人假装哭泣）- 谢谢你，Leslie！
You da man!
你真棒！
[all fake sobbing]
（所有人假装抽泣）
Okay, all we have to do is put the real Foot Rides
好了，我们只需要把真正的Foot Rides
back in the box and get out.
放回盒子里然后离开。
Be strong.
要坚强。
[toilet flushing]
（马桶冲水声）
- Doorbell! - That's the toilet!
- 门铃响了！- 那是马桶！
- Doyle's still here! - Hide!
- Doyle还在这里！- 快躲起来！
♪ ♪
That's right, Ma, Le Doorbell Suite.
没错，妈妈，这是《门铃套房》。
Mm-hmm. Where's the ice bucket?
嗯哼。冰桶在哪儿？
It's got to be around here somewhere.
一定就在这附近的某个地方。
Oh! There it is, right in front of my eyes.
哦！就在我眼前。
What's that? The view?
那是什么？风景吗？
Let's just open up the old curtains
让我们打开旧窗帘
and take a look-see, huh?
看看外面，怎么样？
Ah. Wait a minute. Who's this little fella?
啊。等一下。这个小家伙是谁？
It's a ladybug! That means good luck.
是瓢虫！那意味着好运。
Which I didn't have with my new Apollo odor-proof socks.
我穿了我的阿波罗防臭袜，结果并没有带来好运。
I had the Denver Yetis test them out, and, uh...
我让丹佛野兽队测试了一下，呃...
odor-proof they are not.
它们并不防臭。
Whoo! All right, look, my boss will be here any minute
哇！好吧，看，我的老板随时会来
for my big presentation.
参加我的重要报告。
I'm gonna get my sport coat on.
我要穿上我的运动夹克。
All righty.
好的。
And...ooh! I forgot my tie.
哦！我忘了我的领带。
[doorbell chimes]
[门铃响]
All right, Ma, look, she's here.
好了，妈，看，她来了。
I gotta go. Uh-huh. Yeah.
我得走了。嗯哼。是的。
Okay.
好的。
That was close, right, Dawn?
刚才好险，对吧，Dawn？
Where'd Dawn go?
Dawn去哪儿了？
She must be in the safe.
她一定在保险箱里。
If she's in the safe, we have much bigger problems.
如果她在保险箱里，我们就有更大的问题了。
Not as big as that one.
没有那个大。
Dad?
爸爸？
I see you two have met.
看来你们俩已经认识了。
Yes, we rode up in the elevator together.
是的，我们一起坐电梯上来的。
I sneezed. He didn't say "bless you."
我打了个喷嚏。他没说“保佑你”。
Can we move this along?
我们能快点进行吗？
Uh, of course, of course, Ms. Apollo, and, uh,
呃，当然，当然，阿波罗女士，而且，呃，
I can't wait to see your face when you open that box.
我迫不及待想看你打开那个盒子时的表情。
This is bad.
这很糟糕。
When she opens that box,
当她打开那个盒子时，
all she's gonna find are slippers.
她只会找到拖鞋。
Well, if they're half as good as Doyle says, I think we'll...
嗯，如果它们有道尔说的那么好的一半，我想我们会...
- [sneezes] [Ricky] Bless you.
- [打喷嚏] [瑞奇] 保佑你。
I know that "bless you."
我知道那个“保佑你”。
That's the fastest bless in the west.
那是西部最快的祝福。
- Oh, boys! - Get him!
哦，孩子们！抓住他！
Oh! Oh, I'm sorry!
哦！哦，对不起！
[Ms. Apollo] I don't believe what I'm seeing.
我不敢相信我看到的。
Sorry, these are just... my kids.
对不起，这些只是...我的孩子们。
They just won a laundromat competition.
他们刚刚赢得了一个洗衣店比赛。
Not them, that!
不是他们，是那个！
Hey.
嘿。
That would...also be my kid.
那也会...是我的孩子。
Wow, she got sick air!
哇，她吸到了生病的空气！
True dat.
确实如此。
How'd you even get up there?
你是怎么爬上去的？
Um...I'm glad you asked!
嗯...很高兴你问了！
You ever look at a regular pair of shoes and think,
你有没有看着一双普通的鞋子，然后想，
"Man, I wish I could jump all the way
“天哪，我真希望能用它们跳到吊扇那么高？”
to the ceiling fan with those?"
那么，现在你可以了，用Sweet Foot Rides。
Well, now you can, with Sweet Foot Rides.
这是你演示的一部分吗？
Is this part of your presentation?
是--不--可能--
Ye--no--may--
这很聪明。
- It's very clever. - Yes.
是的。
What else can those Sweet Foot Rides do?
Sweet Foot Rides还能做什么？
Uh...why don't you tell her, Dad?
呃...你为什么不告诉她，爸爸？
Um, well, I am also glad you asked.
嗯，好吧，我很高兴你问了。
Those are just the jumper attachments.
那些只是跳跃附件。
But Sweet Foot Rides can do so much more, for example--
但Sweet Foot Rides能做的远不止这些，例如——
[all yell]
[所有人喊叫]
[Dawn groaning]
[Dawn呻吟]
That was also part of the presentation.
那也是演示的一部分。
Keep going.
继续。
Uh, why cart around ten different types of shoes
呃，为什么要带着十种不同类型的鞋子到处跑
when all you need is one Sweet Foot Ride?
当你只需要一双甜美的脚步之旅时，为什么要带着十种不同类型的鞋子呢？
- [sneezes] - Bless you!
——阿嚏——保佑你！
- Beat you! - Ugh!
——赢你！——呃！
♪ ♪
We're not happy you lied.
我们对你撒谎并不感到高兴。
And snuck into someone's hotel room.
还偷偷进入了别人的酒店房间。
Twice.
两次。
And worst of all,
最糟糕的是，
you lied about winning a laundromat competition.
你撒谎说赢得了一个洗衣店比赛。
But I have to admit, if it weren't for you kids pushing me,
但我必须承认，如果不是你们这些孩子推动我，
I never would have shown those shoes to Doyle.
我绝不会把那些鞋子展示给多伊尔看。
He thinks they're gonna be huge sellers.
他认为它们会成为热销品。
- We're gonna be gold jet rich! - Whoo!
我们要发大财了！
- Yes! - Hey, hey, hey, not so fast.
是的！
I told you, you don't get rich overnight.
我告诉过你，你不会一夜暴富的。
No, first they have to be tested by the Apollo sneakerologists.
不，首先它们得被阿波罗运动鞋专家测试。
How long will that take? Three or four weeks?
那需要多长时间？三到四周？
Three or four years.
三到四年。
[all groaning]
[众人叹气]
But, but, but, in the meantime,
但是，在此期间，
we can live like we're Doorbell Suite rich.
我们可以像住在门铃套房一样富有地生活。
[doorbell melody]
[门铃旋律]
Now make it sound like a toilet.
现在让它听起来像厕所。
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪